Guide to the William Nicoson papers, 1954-2007
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 3: Federal, 1960-1980; (3 boxes)
  - Excerpt from Statement of George Romney Secretary of Housing and Urban Development (HUD) before the Subcommittee on Economy in Government of the JOint Economic Committee on Changing Nation Priorities-June 16, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    330.04
  - U.S. Government Memorandum from Sidney Gardner Secretary for Community Development-June 23, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    330.07
  - The Minneapolis Tribune Volume CIV, Number 36: Article titled New Towns and National Growth-June 29, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    330.08
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) Clip Sheets-July, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    330.10
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD News: The High Price of Polarization-June 30, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    330.09
  - Press Release from White House Press Conference by Nation Goals Research President Leonard Garment and Dr. Daniel P. Moynihan and Raymon A. Bauep-July 18 (2 copies), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    330.20
  - Housing and Urban Development/Summary of Financing Provisions for Le Vaudreuil Program-July 30, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    330.22
  - Architectural and Engineering Services for Metropolitan Planning and Development Programs-August, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    330.25
  - Maumelle New Town: Housing and Urban Development (HUD) Loan Would Give New Impetus to Planned Community by Bobbie Foster, Arkansas Democrat-August 16, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    330.26
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) Vaudreuil Mission Report-September 16, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    330.30
  - Housing and Urban Development, Selected Elements of Municipal Finance-September, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    330.29
  - Housing and Urban Development/Vaudreuil Project-October 27, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    330.23
  - Proposal: New Cities and Transportation, The Institute for the Future Riverview Center-April, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    329.16
  - Housing and Urban Development-Census of Population and Housing, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    328.16
  - Domestic Growth Task Force, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    328.18
  - Domestic Growth Task Force, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    328.19
  - Domestic Growth Task Force, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    328.20
  - Domestic Growth Task Force, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    328.21
  - Domestic Growth (Presidential Message), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    328.17
  - Establishing a District of Columbia Urban Development Corporation-December 14, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    334.09
  - Congressional Record-Senate: Minnesota and Urban Development-November 18, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    334.05
  - Congressional Record-Senate: New Towns and Private Enterprise-November 16, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    334.04
  - Minnesota Experimental City Report to national Steering Committee, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    332.01
  - Housing and Urban Development Vaudreuil Center for Urban Pollution Research-May 3, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    333.08
  - Urban Report/Capitol Hill Activists Work on Plan to Share Policy Role From Housing and Urban Development (HUD) by William Lilley III-January 9, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    333.01
  - Urban Housing and Transportation: A New Partnership by Wilfred Owen, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    332.02
  - Government Subsidized Housing, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    332.06
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) Clip Sheets-January, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    335.06
  - Housing and Urban Development/Real Estate Research Corporation-January 13, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    335.07
  - Report of the National Policy Task Force, Architectural Record-February, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    335.10
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development/Mr. William Nicoson (Consultant), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    334.12
  - Report on National Growth, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    334.11
  - Rockefeller Proposal, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    334.15
  - Rockefeller Proposal, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    334.16
  - Rural Development-Department of Agriculture, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    337.03
  - Legislation, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    337.04
  - U.S. House/Witness List for Oversight Hearings on the Housing and Urban Development (HUD) New Communities-May 30-31, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    337.07
  - U.S. House/Oversight Hearings-May, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    337.06
  - Sangster Task Force Papers, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    336.05
  - National Institute of Building Sciences (NIBS) Workshop, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    340.13
  - House Hearing-Columbus Meeting, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    420.5
    - Report/Speech: William J. Nicoson, September 29, 1975; 1.
    - Report: Academy for Contemporary Problems, June 1975; 2.
  - Design of The New Communities Program: A Background Paper for the New Communities Administration Housing and Urban Development (HUD) by William Nicoson and Associated Papers-September 28, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    339.13
  - Design of The New Communities Program: A Background Paper for the New Communities Administration Housing and Urban Development (HUD) by William Nicoson and Associated Papers-September 28, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    339.12
  - Urban Land Institute (ULI) Meeting-New Communities Council Meeting Minutes, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    340.01
  - Housing and Urban Development Policy, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    340.07
  - Human Urban Technology-Summer, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    340.09
  - Williams Housing and Urban Development Growth Report, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    340.08
  - Housing Subcommittee-Urban Script, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    340.10
  - Plan Analysis Session of the National Realty Committee, Incorporated-October 18, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    341.10
  - Growth Policy Report Summary-September 5, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    341.09
  - Site and Neighborhood Design Briefing U.S. Department of Energy Region III, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    341.13
- Series 4: International, 1957-1979; (4 boxes)
  The series covers a variety of international new towns from France, Swede and others. Most of the information is brochures, maps and statistics from the international new towns.
  - Vallingby, Sweden, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    327.09
  - Issues in European New Town Development, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 13)
    326.22
  - Regional Economy Policy in the Federal Republic of Germany, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 14)
    326.20
  - Stockholm City-Lower Norrmalm, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 15)
    327.23
  - Background in Urbanization Problems in Finland, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 16)
    327.05
  - Sweden, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    320.05
  - British New Towns by Fred McLaughlin and Leonard Siegalman-September 25, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    327.16
  - Town Planning in Sweden-A Short Survey, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    327.21
  - Stockholm-Information Service: The City of Stockholm, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    327.22
  - Skarholmen-June by Albert Aronson, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    327.24
  - United Kingdom, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    321.02
  - Sweden, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    320.21
  - Finland: Maps and Booklets, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    319.01
  - Swedish Booklet, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    320.06
  - The Political and Financial Problems of New Towns, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 4)
    339.01
  - Institutional Innovation in New Towns: The Dual Developer Concept, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 5)
    339.04
  - Federal Republic of Germany, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 6)
    336.04
  - Planning and Programming Housing Activities, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 7)
    333.11
  - United Kingdom Booklet, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 8)
    321.04
  - United Kingdom: Hertford Bircherley Green Redevelopment, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 9)
    321.01
  - United Kingdom: Moss Side, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 10)
    321.06
  - United Kingdom: Thamesmead, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 11)
    320.24
  - Sweden: Neighborhood Map, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 12)
    320.16
  - Sweden: Neighborhood Map, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 13)
    320.13
  - Sweden: Booklet, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 14)
    320.11
  - Sweden: Brochure, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 15)
    320.08
  - Italy: Booklet, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 16)
    320.04
  - Holland: Facts and Figures, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 17)
    320.03
  - Sweden: New Towns on the Bottom of the Sea, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 18)
    320.02
  - Holland: Planning and Creation of an Environment, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 19)
    320.01
  - Germany: Community Brochure, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 20)
    319.10
  - France: Map, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 21)
    319.07
  - France: Map, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 22)
    319.06
  - France: Booklet, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 23)
    319.05
  - Information on the Physical Planning in Stockholm-June, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    330.02
  - Study Mission for the New City of Vaudreuil-June 18, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    330.06
  - Vaudreuil Summary-July 9, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    330.15
  - General Briefing Book for Mr. William Nicoson (European Mission: United Kingdom, France and Holland)-July 10-21, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    330.17
  - Housing and Urban Development Office of International Affairs-Translating of "Vaudreuil"-August 24, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    330.28
  - Directions for Preparation of Municipal Housing, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    329.02
  - Information on the Physical Planning in Stockholm, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    329.04
  - Suburb General Layout Plan for Northern Jarvafalt, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    329.05
  - Suburb Plan for the Suburban Group of Southern Jarvafalt: Rinkeby and Tensta, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    329.06
  - France, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    329.08
  - Status Report on U.S./France Cooperative Program, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    329.10
  - La Prevention "Anti-Nuisances" Dans La Ville (Principals Recommendations)-April, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    329.18
  - Summary of Proposed Program for a New Community in Amberst-May, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    329.19
  - Note D'Information Sur La Ville Nouvelle Du Vaudreuil-May 27, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    329.22
  - The Renewal of Town Centers in Sweden, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    320.17
  - Sweden: Booklet, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    320.07
  - Finland: Helsinki Master Plan Proposal, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    319.02
  - Sweden: Brochures (2 copies), 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    320.19
  - A Study of Environmental Conditions and Problems Encountered in a Metropolitan Region and Zone-France, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    332.07
  - French New Towns, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    332.08
  - Foreign Travel, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    332.10
  - Fact Sheets on Sweden, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    320.23
  - Fact Sheets on Sweden, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    320.22
  - The Swedish Budget, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    320.10
  - Soviet Union-United Kingdom, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    334.17
  - Housing and Urban Development International-Special Supplement: The Problems Associated with Rapid Urban Growth-January 20th, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    335.08
  - Environment Planning and Conservatism in Sweden-March, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    335.13
  - Urban Land Use Law and Planning in the Netherlands-The Conservation Foundation, International Comparative Land Use Program, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    339.02
  - Urban Land Use Law and Planning in the Netherlands-The Conservation Foundation, International Comparative Land Use Program, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    339.03
  - Sources-French Development Districts, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    338.08
  - Sweden: Brochure, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    320.09
  - Paris Congress, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    339.09
  - University of Manchester-German Planning School-August 31, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    339.10
  - British Association for the Advancement of Science-September 3, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    339.11
  - Land Policy in Sweden, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    320.20
  - Sweden: Booklets (2 copies), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    320.15
  - Germany: Booklet, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    319.09
  - France: Booklets (2 copies), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    319.03
  - Joint Committee Point-Recent Development in French Planning-Some Lessons for the U.S., 1977 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    340.02
  - Commisian-La Construire Building, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    340.03
  - Commission-La Construire Building, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    340.04
  - Commission II-La Gerer Managing, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    340.05
  - Commission La Vivre, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    340.06
  - United Kingdom: Town and Country Planning, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    320.28
  - United Kingdom: Inner Cities of Tomorrow, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    320.27
  - United Kingdom: Discussion Paper, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    320.26
  - Germany: Neue Heimat, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    319.14
  - Germany: Bockenheim, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    319.12
  - Germany: Bockenheim, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    319.11
  - Germany: Frankfurt Brochure, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    319.08
  - East Hertfordshire District Council-June, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    340.15
  - Association Internationale des Ville Nouvelles, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    340.16
  - United Kingdom: Central Lancashire Development Corporation, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    321.05
  - Sweden: Brochure, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    320.14
  - Sweden: Building Statistics, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    320.12
  - France: Riboud, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    319.04
  - Association Internationale des Villes Nouvelles, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    341.11
  - United Kingdom: New Town Bulletin, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    321.03
  - United Kingdom: Ingol Golf Village, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    321.08
  - United Kingdom: The New Towns of Britain, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    321.07
  - United Kingdom: Town and Country Planning Association, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    320.25
  - Swedish Civil Engineering, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    320.18
  - Germany: Neue Heimat, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    319.13
- Series 5: Newsclipping, 1960-1985; (2 boxes)
  The articles in this collection are mostly from newspapers about different new towns. Also in the series are articles written by people involved in new town development.
  - Industrial Opportunity...Lies Between Dulles International Airport and Capitol Hill in Fairfax County, Virginia, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 11)
    326.13
  - City from Scratch by David Winder, Milton Keynes, England, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 12)
    328.13
  - Population in Suburbs Show Heave Increases, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 13)
    328.14
  - The Messianic Master Builder by James Rouse and his Instant City, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Financing of New Towns by Michael B. Glick, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 15)
    328.09
  - Rebuilding and Building Anew by Simon Jensfelt, Deputy City Architect of Stockholm, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 16)
    326.05
  - New Towns for America: Their General Advantages to Citie and Their People by Frederick Gutheim, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 17)
    326.15
  - Washington World-October, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    323.25
  - Life Magazine, Volume 59, Number 26-December 24, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    327.08
  - New Town Seminar Working Session III and IV-August 13, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    327.07
  - Close-up/Piet Helen Bestrides Art and Science, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    327.10
  - Newsweek-May 9, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    327.11
  - The Washington Post-October 29, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    341.17
  - The Washingtonian-February, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    323.40
  - The Reston Times-April 15, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    323.45
  - City Builder by Benjamin Ruhe: The Washington Star-May 8, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    323.46
    - "City Builder", Sunday Magazine, The Washington Star, May 8, 1966; 1.
  - The Reston News-November 17, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    324.02
  - Are WE Being En-Gulfed? by Wolf Von Eckardt, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    326.12
  - The Mirage of New Towns: Housing-Can We Do Better? by William Alonso, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    326.03
  - The Washington Post-march 5, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    327.12
  - The Washington Post-June 3, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    327.15
  - The Washington Post-April 30, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    327.14
  - the Washington Post-April 2, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    327.13
  - New Town Development and the Theory of Location by Bruce Ricks, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    328.12
  - New Communities: A Vital Program, A Good Investment by Edward M. Lamont, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    328.08
  - New Towns and Old Ideas by W.G. Grigsby-November 18, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    327.18
  - The Sydney Morning Herald-February 18, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    324.06
  - The Future of Urban Transportation II by John K. Kain and John R. Meyer, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    327.19
  - Automotive Information: Volume 6, Number 2-October, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    327.25
  - How Now, New Towns? by Frederick Gutneim-November 14, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    327.26
  - The Reston Times-October 4, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    324.15
  - The Washington Post-April 20, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    324.14
  - Saipa: Journal for Public Administration, South African Institute for Public Administration, Volume 4, Number 3-June, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    328.01
  - The Washington Post-October 5, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    328.03
  - What are New Towns for? by William Alonso-October, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    328.02
  - The New Community Plan; Development "New Communities" With Second Income Plan Financing Techniques by Norman G. Kurland, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    327.27
  - Land Policy and Development by Torsten Ljungberger, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    327.29
  - Clippings, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 10)
    323.36
  - Congress Gives Boost to New Town Building, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 11)
    327.28
  - European New Towns: One Answer to Urban Problems? by Jack A. Underhill, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 12)
    326.09
  - New Town Bucks U.S. Trends-Columbia, Maryland-Home Sales Soar and Industry Keeps Pace by George H. Favre, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 13)
    326.18
  - Lock at Americas "New Towns!" by Wolfagang Langewiesche, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 14)
    326.14
  - Focus on Northern Virginia, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 15)
    326.11
  - Outline of Statement to majors on Advantages of New Communities, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 16)
    326.04
  - Clippings, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 17)
    336.09
  - Tuy Medio by Alan Turner, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 18)
    341.16
  - Newsclippings, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 19)
    324.16
  - The Bankers Magazine Spring, Volume 153, Number 2-Building and the Two Factor Theory, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    329.15
  - CPR National Journal, Office of New Communities-February 4, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    329.13
  - Modeling School Facility Requirements in New Communities by Charles M. Easement and Kenneth O. Kortanek-January, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    329.12
  - The Christian Science Monitor, People in Motion and the Route They Take-October 16, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    330.31
  - Business Week, Making Cities Better Places To Five-August 22, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    330.27
  - What Is This Thing Called Urban Growth Policy? by Donald Canty-August/September, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - The Washington Post, Census Paints Mural of a Changing Nation by Richard Harwood-July 20, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    330.21
  - "Toward Balanced Growth Quantity with Quality" Summary of the Report to the President by the National Growth Research Staff-July 18, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    330.19
  - The New York Times, Black Exodus to Suburbs-July 12, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    330.18
  - The Washington Post, Charles County 'New City' Due-July 2, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    330.11
  - Cybernetics in City Hall: An Understanding of the principles of Cybernetics Can Guide Fundamental Improvements in Urban Government by E.S. Savas, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    329.23
  - The Mortgage Banker, Why Columbia Succeeded Where Others Failed by Lowell E. Sunderland-June, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    330.01
  - Architectural Forum-Technology: New Towns are our Mandate for Urban Innovation by Sumner Myers and Robert Schwartz-June, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    329.24
  - A Tale of New Cities by Samuel Jackson-May 23, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    329.21
  - The Reston Times-January 1, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    324.23
  - Geotimes: News of the Earth Sciences-December, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    324.24
  - The Washington Post, Planner Lauds Provisions of 'New Town' Legislation-January 16, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    333.02
  - U.S. News and World Report, More Millions for New Cities/Towns-January 18, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    333.03
  - Congressional Record-Extension of Remarks, Experimental City by Donald M. Frase (Senator-Minnesota)-December 3, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    334.07
  - The Building Official and Code Administration, How it's Done in Sweden-August, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    333.12
  - Journal of Community Development Society, Volume 2, Number 2, New Towns and Citizen Participation: A Policy Analysis by Richard O. Brooks, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Decade of Disillusion by Eldridge H. Lovelace-November 4, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    334.03
  - City Winter, The First Meeting of the Regional New Towns Committee by James A. Clapp, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    334.06
  - The Washington Post-November 28, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    324.25
  - Caveat Empter in Real Estate Equities by Samuel L. Hayes III and Leonard M. Harlan, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    326.16
  - Education in New Cities by Myran Lieberman-March, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    335.12
  - New York, Mickey Mouse for Mayor: The Only Way to Have Fun City Urban-Design-Wise is to take it from the Do-Gooders and Lease it to the Disney People by Peter Blake-February 7, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    325.11
  - Herndon Tribune-February 9, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    324.27
  - The Washington Post, Wright Tract-January 15, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    324.26
  - Virginia Cardinal-August, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    324.29
  - Conservation Foundation-December, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    339.08
  - Ladies Home Journal, 15 Best Suburbs-August, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    324.31
  - The Fairfax Journal, Bourbon Mamefacturing Plant-January 1, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    324.35
  - The Herndon Observer, Volume II, Number 19-December 16, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    324.42
  - Fountain Suit Settled OUr of Court/Lake Anne Landmark Returns-March 2, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    324.43
  - The Reston Times-October 19, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    324.44
  - Autumn Reston Homeowners Association (RHOA), 1979 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    324.46
  - The Reston Times-May 24, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    324.47
  - The Washington Post, A Suburb That Saves Energy By Happy Accident by Thomas Grubisich-July 21, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    324.48
  - The Washingtonian-November, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    325.03
  - The Reston Times-October 30, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    325.02
  - The Washington Post, Religion, United Christian Church: A simple Local Approach-August 1, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    325.09
  - The Reston Times-April 2, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    325.08
  - Lake Anne Village Advertisement-March 6, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    325.07
  - Clippings-February, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    325.06
  - Peaceful Pathway, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    323.22
  - Newsclippings, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - The Reston Times-February 4, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    325.12
  - The Reston Times-February 11, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    325.13
  - Washington Business, Tax Breaks May Help Virginia Distiller Break Even on Ethanol Venture-July 26, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    325.15
  - The Reston Times, A Complete Guide to Reston-August 5, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    325.17
  - The Connection, Christmas at Lake Anne Plaza-December 1, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    325.20
  - The Reston Times-December 2, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    325.21